<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="prog_info">
        Service name:EluoC&#38;C Intranet\n\n
        version: Release Version 1.6.3\n\n
        Function:\n
        - Top 5 list of notices on main screen\n
        - Show holiday on Main Screen\n
        - Show External Working Information Output List on Main Screen\n
        - In the main screen, new announcements are displayed in the notification list for 7 days.\n
        - Device user information sajin / department / department\n
        - Provides contents of contents of 20 company notices\n
        - In the search results of the company"'"s employee information search, click the Details link to send jeonhwa \n
        - Search for search function with telephone / name / ID when searching for employees in the Company"'"s Search menu\n
        - Touch and hold for longer than 3 seconds in the Company"'";s employee search results list to connect to the phone.\n
        - Enable search for employees "'" search voice recognition\n
        - Provides checking of my holiday history \n
        - Meeting the contents of the conference room reservation function\n
        - Provide contents of employee information when receiving phone call\n
        - The push notification is received according to the scheduling time of the conference room.
        \n\n
        Around:\n
        - The app includes ELUOC&#38;C If you are not an employee, it will not function normally during installation.\n
        - The app includes ELUOC&#38;C Intranet The app will not be used as an additional purpose (2nd processing).\n
        - The app includes ELUOC&#38;C  Here are some applications that have been developed during the internal learning process.\n
        \n
        \n
        history\n
        Version:  Release Version 1.6.3\n
        1. Fix multimedia errors\n
        \n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.6.2\n
        1. Bug tracking added.\n
        2. Add the top of the main screen, notice more features
        \n\n

        Version: Release Version 1.6.1\n
        1. No mobile status display on the main screen\n
        2. Corrected error on New list in main list\n
        3. Add multi-window related phrases\n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.6\n
        1. Main screen is screen ratio processing by Android device.\n
        2. New announcement in main screen notice list added new display for 7 days
        3. 18:9 response. Additional support for 18.5:9 by adding additional support
        4. Layout setting function
        \n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.5\n
        1. Add voice recognition search capability to search for employees\n
        2. The colour change has been changed according to the display of the main screen gongji information.\n
        3. Added animated effects for screen movement\n
        4. Screen inteuro Image Replacement
        \n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.4\n
        1. Added function related to conference room scheduling function
        \n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.3\n
        1. Added Push token acquisition function\n
        2. No employee information results processed error correction.
        \n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.2\n
        1. Push function added\n
        2. Ability to deal with features related to Android 7.0
        \n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.1\n
        1. Touch event error modified if no employee inquiry results
        \n\n

        Version:  Release Version 1.0\n
        1. Once Phone is received, a layer pop-up will occur, and when the phone terminates, it will disappear\n\n



    </string>
</resources>